Guide to the West Coast Punk and New Wave Club flyers, ca 1979-1982.
West Coast Punk and New Wave Club flyers,
- Fliers and posters, 1978-1989
  - Flipper, Bad Posture, Hellation, Allies, Undated; Illustrated with a photo collage featuring workers on river boats (Box 1, Folder 4)
    At Sounds of Music, May 8
  - The Enemy, 1980-07-17-1980-07-19; Illustrated with a pixelated photograph of a woman (Box 1, Folder 4)
    At Fab Mab
  - Marc Huestis’ Film: X-Communication, Undated; Illustrated with a photograph of a parachuter (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Musik by Factrix. Performances by Erich Brogger, Marshall Rheiner, Silvana Nova. DoorDie!
  - Reagan, Undated; Illustrated with a photograph of Hitler (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Dark Side of Pop on Broadway, 1980-06-10; Illustrated with a drawing of two vampires (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Dead Kennedys, 1979-10-06-1984-10-06; Illustrated with a drawing of John F. Kennedy (Box 1, Folder 4)
    L.A. Alley Cats and Bags
  - Secret Service, 1980-04-20; Illustrated with a photograph of a gun on a police report; design to Zonk Design (Box 1, Folder 4)
    At PALMS
  - The Lewd. Breakouts, Mindsweeper, 1980-09-23; Illustrated with drawings of cock roaches and a man drumming (Box 1, Folder 4)
    At Rock City
  - The Machine. Rolling, reaches you, penetrating, Undated; Illustrated with a photo collage featuring images of war and experiments; blue stock (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Pleasurable! Silvertone, 1980-04-24-1980-04-25; Illustrated with photograph of the band (Box 1, Folder 4)
    At Broadway Theatre
  - The Misfits. With Toxic Reasons from Dayton, Ohio, 1981-11-21; Illustrated with a drawing of a skull (Box 1, Folder 4)
    At Severely Muted (used to be Sound of Music)
  - Poetry. Open Reading, Wine, Donation. Saturday Night Poetry Series, 1980-12-06-1980-12-13; Illustrated with a drawing of a Californian Missionary (Box 1, Folder 4)
    At Panjandrum
  - Stingers with the Speed Queens, 1980-07-10; Illustrated with a photo collage of young adults (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Rare Disorder Makes Victims Act Like Raving Lunatics. The truth about sex, drugs, discipline. The possibilities are endless. At Pippins
  - Democracy, Undated; Illustrated with a photo collage featuring an American flag fashioned into a gun (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Read the Fine Print. Drums along the maple wood. Featuring Shari Famous and Chusid. Other vocal and instruments by La Bonte and Paramoxie Invisibles., Undated; Illustrated with a photo collage featuring images of celebrities, butchers, and a dollar bill (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - No Alternative, Tools, False Idols, Breakouts, 1980-04-05; Illustrated with a drawing of a blindfolded man (Box 1, Folder 4)
    At Dew Drop Inn
  - July, Undated; Illustrated with a photo collage featuring a model in a bathing suit (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Golden Gate Jumpers, X-iles, Passions, Balls, Titans, Neasden Knights, Questions, Wasp Women, The Enemy, Good Samaritans, M.C., Timmy Spence, Lloyds, VIPs, Cha-Cha-Billy, Jim Carroll Band, Romeo Void, Valkays. At Back D.O.R.
  - Hashbury Neighbors New Art Show, 1980-04-03-1980-04-28; Illustrated with small drawing of abstract objects hanging on a clothing line (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Los Microwaves, 1980-01; Illustrated with photograph of dollar bills (Box 1, Folder 4)
    At Back D.O.R., Fab Mabuhay, and Van Ness
  - Prefix Society Dog, 1980-10-07; Illustrated with a photo collage featuring woman and shoes (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Stop and Consider Your Future. Don’t Read this before going to bed [you may not sleep]. Christian people, pray God to save America before it is too late. At Sound of Music
  - Pointed Sticks, 1980-04-18-1980-04-24; Illustrated with a drawing of a dog wearing a gas mask (Box 1, Folder 4)
    At Fab Mab and Back D.O.R.
  - Roberto Vargas and Ken Forde. Will present a benefit reading for Nethula Journal, 1980-08-21; Illustrated with a pencil drawing by Juan Fuentes, entitled “Cancion de Liberacion,” of a man playing the flute (Box 1, Folder 4)
    At Woodrow Wilson International Center
  - LongShoreman, Dog Town, Oblong Rhondes, Myke Reilly, Undated; Illustrated with a photo collage featuring a photograph of a rally, and a photograph of a work camp (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Untitled, Undated; Illustrated with a question mark with a globe as the point (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Untitled, Undated; Illustrated with a clock with a swinging globe part (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Hostage Rescue Disaster: Agents infiltrated Iran. No U.S. forces in Iran, Carter says, 1980-04-30; Illustrated with the front cover of a newspaper (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Outer Limits: Dance Away Wednesday Thru [sic] Sunday, Undated; Illustrated with a man in a suit dancing (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Longshorman, Dogtown, Oblong Rhondes, Myke Reilly, Undated; Illustrated with three photographs: trash, several women in the back of a pickup truck, and a coffee truck (Box 1, Folder 4)
    At Clubfoot, March 20
  - &, Undated; Photo collage featuring man laying on floor (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Eye Con: A Series of Horologic Bytes, 1980-04-01-1980-04-29; Illustrated with a drawing of eyeglasses, attributed to Tresivad (Box 1, Folder 4)
    At The Postcard Palace
  - Fascist, Undated; Illustrated with a photograph of a man with a bottle of liquor (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - No Draft…No War, Undated; Illustrated with a photo collage featuring text, soldiers, and a man visiting a cemetery (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 7080, Undated; Illustrated with a drawing of musical notes (Box 1, Folder 4)
    At The Mab and Le Disqu
  - The Readymades. Little Rodger and The Dots, The Psychotic Pineapple, 1979-07-07-1984-07-07; Drawings of couples dancing (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Controllers. The Urge. Avengers, 1979-05-18-1984-05-18 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Dead Kennedys and the Germs, with The Imposters, 1978-11-04-1989-11-04; Text only, various typefaces (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Psyclone Presents, The Dogs, Undated; Black and white images of The Dogs band members (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Nu—Models Sleepers, Undated; Illustrated, image of young couple; yellow stock (Box 1, Folder 5)
    At Back D.O.R.oor, Jan. 4th and 6th
  - The Teenage. With $27 Snap On Face, 1978-02-20-1984-02-20; Illustrated, school yearbook motif (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Dils. Plus Uxa and Sleepers, 1978-04-22 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Dils. With Negative Trend and JJ 180, 1978-08-28 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Statics. Negative trend. Ointment, 1978-02-27 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Benefit May 21st “Riot” Defense Fund. The Offs. Blowdryers, 1978-08-31; Illustrated with image of burning police car (Box 2, Folder 5)
    At The Deaf Club
  - The Filmmaker’s Cinemetheque Presents An Evening with David Wise, 1966-12-24; Hand-lettered text (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Dils. Contractions. Alley Cats. Crime. Weirdos. GoGos, 1979-09-29 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    At Fillmore
  - Rock On OK!. The Heartbreakers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Leila and the Snakes, Undated; Illustrated on peach stock (Box 2, Folder 5)
    May 9th, at Alcazar theatre
  - Punk Rock, the New Wave is in. Send for your How to Look Punk guide, 1970-04-11-1981-04-11; Montage of music notices, advertisements (Box 2, Folder 5)
    At Subterranean
  - Mutants Off. With SSI and Contractions, Undated; Multiple typefaces (Box 2, Folder 5)
    October 31st
  - A Night of Electro Psycho Rock with The Screamers, Tuxedomoon and The Units, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    May 25, at California Hall
  - Co-Stars Mutants and Plugz, with Dead Kennedys, 1978-09-28-1989-09-28; Multiple typefaces (Box 2, Folder 5)
    At Mahubay Gardens
  - Tuxedomoon. Levi and The Rockats, 1979-09-07-1984-09-07 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Avengers. With Negativity Trends and Flesheaters, 1978-08-22 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Leila and the Snakes. Mutants plus Lucky Stiffs, 1978-07-20 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Mutants plus Special Guest Steve Weizzer, 1978-03-23 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Lewds. Breakouts. Mindsweeper, 1980-09-23 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Ever-Popular Fleshapoids along with Ivy and tyhe eaters and Pressure, 1979-05-25; Hand-lettered text (Box 2, Folder 5)
    At Golden Gate Park
  - Dead Kennedys, DOA, 1979-05-26 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Dogs in Heat, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    February 10-11, at Mabuhay Gardens
  - Tuxedomoon, Levi and The Rockats, DOA, 1979-09-01; Printed on blue stock (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Gun Club. Top Jimmy and Rik L. Rik, 1980-07-13; Illustrated, with group of ca. 1950s immigrant protestors (Box 2, Folder 5)
    At Hong Kong Caf
  - Tuxedomoon, Plimpsolus, Factrix, 1980-01-18; Illustrated, printed in yellow and black (Box 2, Folder 5)
    At Roosevelt
  - Gun Club, Suburban Lawns, 1981-07-12; Illustrated with image of British policeman arresting a woman protester (Box 2, Folder 5)
    At Jett’s Cafe
  - Haute Monde II From One Extreme to Another, 1976-05-01-1982-05-01 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    At Project Artaud Theater.
  - And Now for an Important Message… Toxic Waste, 1981-05-06; Illustrated with skull and cross-bones; multiple typefaces (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Video Metromedia advertisement for documentary showing. Live Music by The Dickheads
  - Calling All Punks, Teds and Rockers!, 1979-04-18-1984-04-18 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Call for protest outside KPFA studio in Berkeley to demand more airtime for punk music
  - Futurama. Madcap Performance, 1980-05-02-1980-05-03 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    2nd Wave at Vorpal
  - The Haters will not be performing anywhere, 1982-02-05 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Multiple typefaces
  - And now for an important message…, 1981; Illustrated in color (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Dr. Video Metromedia advertisement for April-May showings, including C.I.A. Strangelove, All The President’s Men, Nuclear Nightmare, and others
  - The Boss is Back!, Undated; Montage of Hitler in raincoat with fedora against uniform rows of clerical workers (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Incite! Oh Say Can You See, by the Dawn’s Early Light…, Undated; Illustrated, black and white. Six panels withMontages of militarist and capitalist imagery (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - There was a divine plane that created this nation…Ronald Reagan, Undated; Montage of cotton pickers bordered with dollar bills (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Totalmedia Performance. Restrikzion, Undated; On blue stock (Box 2, Folder 6)
    June 21, at Living Art Museum
  - Underground Forces, 1981-11-22-1981-11-23; Illustration dated March 1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Dead Kennedys and other groups. At Roxie theater
  - Untitled, Undated; Images of fractured Stolichniya Vodka and Coca-Cola bottles (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Rock Justice, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    November 12-15 at Old Waldorf
  - Vktms. Social Unrest. Alienation, 1981-02-21; Illustrated with image of piles of skulls from Cambodian genocide (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Untitled, Undated; Montage of three businessmen in suits, a well-dressed woman, alongside industrial imagery and a child playing basketball (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - So You’re Sekptical? Biafra for Mayor, 1979-09-03-1984-09-03 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Dead Kennedy’s poster
  - Blurt with B Team, 1981-11-23 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The Outfits, 1979-05-14-1984-05-14 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Group Material, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Announcement of new location at 132 East 26th St, New York City
  - New Wave Music Film Festival, 1979-10-09 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    At Roxie Cinema
  - On Broadway Theater Nightclub, 1982-04-1982-05 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Announcement of upcoming films (“Model Strikers”) and music acts (Dead Kennedys, Head On, etc)
  - Mercenaries at the Fab Mab, 1980-11-16; Illustrated with 3-panel cartoon of sniper (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Anglosheen, Undated; Illustrated (women in leotards and Elvis) (Box 2, Folder 6)
    July 26, at Jetwave
  - Women Against Repression. A Cultural Benefit for the Committee to Free the Mao Tse-tung Defendants, 1981-10-09; Illustrated (defaced with marker) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The Dark Side of Pop, 1982-01-13; Illustrated with image of woman with drum stick in her mouth (Box 2, Folder 6)
    At the Fab Mab
  - Symptoms. Peter Bilt. Owls, 1981-08-01; Illustrated with image of wild boar in a suit (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The Invertebrates. Repeat Offenders, 1982-11-09; Illustrated with image of well-dressed couple (Box 2, Folder 6)
    On Broadway
  - Michael Peppe. Behaviormusik, 1982-04-23-1982-04-24 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The Temple presents: Tuxedomoon, Black Randy, Mutants, etc., 1980-01-25-1980-01-26; Illustrated with images of bodybuilders (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Theater Workers Present Exception, 1979-10-19; Illustrated in color (Box 2, Folder 6)
    At Project Artaud
  - The Scene. A Guide to Sub-Culture Events in the Bay Area, 1982-03-28-1982-04-03; Illustrated with photoMontage of James Dean and other images (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - ARE. Here’s one I can understand!, 1982-01-19-1982-04-03 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    List of upcoming art exhibitions
  - Fillmore Strutz X The Black. Negative Trend, 1979-04-25-1984-04-25; Illustrated with photoMontage of policeman and a couple at a shooting range (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Jamaican Reggae. Earl Zero and Cornerstone, 1980-07-26; Illustrated in yellow and black with image of lion (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Frank Hymng. Henry Kaiser, 1981-10-09; Illustrated with images of shoes and wristwatch (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Temple Beautiful. Rock Against Racism. Benefit Concert, 1979-06-30-1984-06-30 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Keith Joe Dick. Rockabilly Romeo, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    List of upcoming dates. The Palms October 25, Mabuhay October 27 and October 31
  - Rhode Island School of Design. Graduate Photography Students Exchange Show, 1980-12-01-1980-12-21; Printed in black and lime (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Who’s She? The Fascist Cat on the Rock, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Don’t Worry About It. Edweenä and Bruno S., Undated; Printed in yellow and black (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 30 Years of Imperialist Peace U.S. Style, Undated; Montage showing chronology of U.S. interventions around the globe, and insect’s head (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Ersatz Culture, 1980; 12-panel images of the Mona Lisa with bar codes and a corporate earnings report (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The Agony and Ecstasy of Young Love, 1976; Mock DC comic cover. Inscribed at bottom: “from a Bicentennial Notebook. John Benson, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Carole Graham reading from her new play “Crimes” and poetry by Quentin Hands, 1974-04-20-1985-04-20; Illustrated with drawing of Graham (Box 2, Folder 6)
    At Keystone Korner on Vallejo in North Beach
  - Dick Heads. The Job. Red Asphalt, 1981-09-25 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Tie a Yellow Ribbon…, Undated; Image of CIA effigy lynched from a tree limb by yellow ribbon (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The Invertebrates, Undated; Illustrated with photograph of woman clutching her head (Box 2, Folder 6)
    At San Francisco Art Institute, October 30
  - The Invertebrates. Naked Skinnies, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The Invertebrates. State of Bondage, Undated; Illustrated with Statue of Liberty and erotic motifs (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - bauhaus tsol, 1976-12-15-1982-12-15 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Concert announcement sponsored by KALX, KUSF, and KFJC
  - Coke, Pepsi, Both, Undated; Illustrated with image of pig trodding upon soda bottle cap showing map of the world (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Untitled, Undated; Two black and white images showing forks marked U.S. or U.S.S. R. juxtaposed against clenched fist and strips of map (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Untitled, Undated; Image of Shell gasoline station about to be enveloped by gigantic ocean wave (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Sugar Coated Con Flakes, Undated; Image of cereal bowl containing flakes captioned with cant phrases: “Peace is Our Profession,” “Land of Opportunity, etc" (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Lulu Revue, 1982-07-22 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    At CBGB
  - Untitled, Undated; Image of a mushroom cloud composed of corporate logos (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - SVT. Chrome Dinette, Undated; Lettering (Box 2, Folder 7)
    March 27, at New Oasis Club
  - Palladium nightclub poster, 1986; Pastiche of Anatoly Vasilyev poster, “Under the banner of Lenin we will march to complete victory!” (Box 2, Folder 7)
    In Cyrillic
  - Gnat Music with the Moot Choir, 1980-12-20 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    At Previews
  - Roy Lonex and the Phantom Movers, Undated; Illustrated with photoMontage (Box 2, Folder 7)
    At The I-Beam Club, September 15
  - This is the Army, 1980; Two sheets joined by tape on verso. Image of Hitler speaking in an Uncle Sam hat (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Untitled, Undated; Montage of images of electric razors, spark plug, cola, mouse trap and Rockefeller Center (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Men in Black, 1981-12-31; Montage of werewolf and skeleton (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Act Like Nothing’s Wrong, 1981; Montage of WW II women air raid wardens, large insect, leaping man (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Roxie Benefit Series 1982, 1982; Color illustration of female punk rocker (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - It’s the Real Thing. Coke, Undated; Illustrated with images of Coca-Cola bottles mixed with nuclear warheads bearing the Coke logo (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Untitled, Undated; Illustrated with image of a man at lathe connected to futuristic vehicle, against image of a cityscape (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Militant Entertainment Tour 79. Nazis are No Fun, Undated; Printed on rag paper. Image of a rhino (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Rock Against Racism. Militant Entertainment Tour, 1979; Printed in color on rag paper with image of rhino along with lists of bands (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Rock Against Racism. Our Music! Reggae, Rock ’N’ Roll, Jazz, Funk and Punk, Undated; Printed on rag paper (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Gnat Music. At the Lost Weekend, 1981-03-25; Illustrated with drawing of man at a window (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Contractions, 1981-03-27-1981-03-28; Image of band members (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Symptoms. Los Microwaves. Barry Beam, 1981-11-06; Lettering, illustrated with image of man’s head and barcodes (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Laurie Anderson, 1982-05-04-1982-05-05; Illustrated with image of Anderson (Box 2, Folder 7)
    At Kabuki Theatre
  - Buddy’s Birthday! With the Explosives, 1980-09-07; Printed in four colors, with image of Buddy Holly’s face; some chipping at corners and punctures (Box 2, Folder 7)
    At Le Disque
  - Toward the Future. Anna Banana, Bill Gaglione, Undated; Lettering, montage of man wrapped in paper with “Arte Arte” signs over his eyes (Box 2, Folder 7)
    At Valencia Tool and Die, February 27-28
  - Stop Payment! Direct Current, Undated; Montage of nuclear power plant images (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Anti-nuclear power poster, urging non-payment of electrical utilities
  - Real Estate Show. 123 Delancey Relocated to 172 Delancey, Undated; Illustrated with photo of the property. Spanish-language text, explaining the illegal occupation of the site and the city’s seizure and removal of the occupants’ belongings (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Treason, Undated; Illustrated withMontage of images of police violence against African-Americans (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Keeping the Faith, Undated; Illustrated withMontage of images showing FDR, Joseph McCarthy in bishop’s vestments, Carter and Reagan as altar boys, and three KKK members (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Register Now, Undated; Montage of David Rockefeller superimposed against a wartime image of a devastated city (Box 2, Folder 7)
    David Rockefeller with some straight talk for 19 and 20 year- olds.
  - Just Desserts. Domestic caviar, how tacky! I could just die laughing!, Undated; Montage of three laughing socialites with an arm pointing a gun toward a blindfolded man in tuxedo (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Pepe Moreno. Uncle Sam and the Russian Bear, Undated; Image of Uncle Sam and the Russian Bear seated atop of ship’s smokestack, bobbing in the sea, with explosives strapped to the smokestack bearing the names of Middle East countries (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Cub Foot Condemned. Moving in the Direction of History, Undated; Drawing of a building demolition, with caption quotation of Marian Kester (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - See the Bloc Heads, 1982; Image of G-8 leaders superimposed against globe (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Wild Cards, Undated; Black and white photomontage of card player with Union Jack eyeball, and images of Brixton riots (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - There was a divine plane that created this nation…Ronald Reagan, Undated; Montage of cotton pickers bordered with dollar bills (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - The Great Quake: Political Geology for the 80s, Undated; Montage of two dinosaurs (US and USSR) and two human arms thrusting upward out of the earth (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Men Run America, Undated; Images of TransAmerica Tower superimposed against uniform rows of male-figure symbols (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Revolting Music Group Material, 1970-03-07-1981-03-07; Illustrated with three images of 45-rpm discs (Box 2, Folder 7)
    At Machinist’s Union Hall
  - El Salvador: U.S. Aid Means Death and Torture, Undated; Text with outline of maps of El Salvador and inset of Central America (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Equal Opportunity, Undated; Montage of John Wayne and seven women bearing and firing arms (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Wasp Women. The Dickheads, Undated; Montage of screaming woman and a wasp with woman’s head (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Saturday 27, at On Broadway
  - Lewd. L.A.’s Social Distortion. Lost Cause, 1982-04-09; Black and whiteMontage of band members (Box 2, Folder 7)
    At On Broadway
  - Is God a Triangle. Randy Michel Hussong, 1980-01-28-1980-01-30; Printed in several typefaces, with yellow triangle cloth affixed to paper (Box 2, Folder 7)
    At Jetwave
  - Untitled, Undated; Montage of hand pouring grain into a set of gears containing images of consumerism and capitalist exploitation, with dollar bills flowing out of the gears (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Spiders. The Jobs. Dickheads, 1981-09-26; Illustrated with image of scorpion; chipped at top left (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - The Nuns, 1978-10-20; Various typefaces,Illustrated with image of band members (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Security…Protect Your Sisters, Our Children, Yourself—Think Twice!!, Undated; Five-panel illustrations, in various colors, providing suggestions about protecting the confidentiality of endangered women (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Let Em Eat Bullets. Kids and Guns, Undated; Montage of images of bullets, mushroom clouds, and naked males (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - No More War. The Third Could be the Last, 1981; Montage of sprinter hurdling over the globe, with revolver pointed at him (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Vote, Undated; Image of Reagan with elephant’s nose and tusks (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Lewd. Sheik Vasilino. Golden Gate Jumpers, 1980-06-29; Illustrated with drawing of band members (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Untitled, Undated; Montage of Marlboro Man, with dollar bill and a Vietcong fighter (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Vktms. No Alternative. Tools and Flipper, 1979-11-07-1984-11-07; Illustrated with photograph and multiple typefaces (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Lewd. Also Speed Boys, 1980-05-27-1980-05-28; Drawing of skeleton on motorcycle (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Crime and the Mutants, 1979-05-12; Drawing of criminal with gun (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - It seems like Urbvamp decided to move into liberated territory…, Undated; Drawing depicting armed forces attacking tenant-occupied buildings (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Sunglasses After Dark, 1980-04-10; Illustration of 3-D glasses (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Temple Presents Impatient Youth, Magic Band, 1980-02-29-1980-03-01; Image of Houdini in chains (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Factrix Zev “W/O”, 1981-07-31; Drawing of slaves in chains (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Mary Monday. X’s Annex, 1980-04-12; Photo of Monday; image by Mimi Tierney (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Avengers, 1978-09-09; Images of hammers and nails, multiple typefaces (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Members. Dead Kennedys, Undated; Headshots of band members (Box 2, Folder 8)
    At Old Waldorf, October 28
  - Louder Faster Shorter, 1979-11-17; Illustrated with photo of motorcycle gang members (Box 2, Folder 8)